You said Lok Hiu-sin told you
these alphabets stand for
a high school group called
Youth Investment Organization.
Why did it become IOY?
When was the last time you had a
good, hearty laugh?
You get up each day, go to work,
go to school.
You work your butt off,
doing the same thing.
You try your best against the turmoil
of the world,
then you realized you lost your ability
to laugh.
Don't worry!
We'll make you laugh.
The night after tomorrow at 8 o'clock.
Try not to die laughing.
We have a date.
See you in a place you know best.
They want to do another livestream of death?
(Counting down to the game...)
The last venue for the livestream
is the swimming pool where Ngai Ka-yan died.
They want to re-enact Ngai Ka-yan's death?
What are you looking at?
(Counting down to the game...)
This logo is the same as the pin
you found in Ngai Ka-yan's office.
Are they the real killers?
One of them was in Jarvis' office
and broke the vase.
Let's assume Wendy is one of them,
then the whole thing made sense.
Just think, Wendy was lying.
For a few minutes, no one could
confirm her exact location.
Is it possible she broke the vase
at that time?
Or swapped Ngai Ka-yan's cylinder?
But Wendy is Ngai Ka-yan's diehard fan
and those IOY kids treat Ngai Ka-yan
as their idol
and created a ranking list for him.
Even if they're from the same group,
they have no motive to kill Ngai Ka-yan.
Time to pay the online channel a visit.
These pictures felt like yesterday.
Can't believe what happened to this place.
Gogo Sir, you didn't come to see me, right?
We came to see Wendy.
She hasn't been here for a long time.
Hello?
Gogo Sir, we went to Wendy's flat.
The security guard said she moved out
long time ago.
Thanks.
When was the last time you saw Wendy?
Not since you arrested Auntie Ching.
Did she leave anything behind?
Yes. In the supplies room.
Can we take a look?
How would you describe Wendy's
relationship with Ngai Ka-yan?
Diehard fan with 100% loyalty.
She did everything Jarvis told her to do.
Were they seeing each other?
One of them carrying a torch for the other?
She was Jarvis' diehard fan.
It's normal for her to be crazy about him.
For as long as we've been working together,
never saw them making eyes at each other.
J Weekly uploaded...
a video of Helen having an argument with
Ngai Ka-yan in the playground.
According to Auntie Ching,
Wendy uploaded it.
Wendy accused Auntie Ching of
murdering Ngai Ka-yan
and threatened to report her.
What's your take on this?
Now that she has disappeared,
maybe she's the thief crying the thief
and tried to frame Auntie Ching for murder.
No way. She's an airhead.
If Wendy contacts you, please let us know.
OK!
Hello? Claim Ngai Ka-yan's body?
Wendy...no, Miss Lam is following
up on this.
Miss Lam said she needed to contact
Mr. Ngai's mother who's abroad.
That's why we showed discretion
and extended the deadline.
But it has been three months,
now even Miss Lam has disappeared.
We'd like the online channel to
wrap this up ASAP.
Excuse me, are you with the FEHD?
I'm Ko Man-sum of the Crime Unit,
New Territories East...
Do you recognize her?
Yes! I have never met someone like
Miss Lam who takes things to heart.
She did everything herself
and picked the most expensive item.
She personally picked out the coffin
from the coffin shop.
When you discussed the details
with Miss Lam,
did you notice anything unusual?
She was polite.
But she lost her temper when
we discussed the burial.
I already applied ahead of time,
what's taking so long?
They said it hasn't been done before.
It may be against regulations.
What does that mean? They won't approve it?
I don't care how much it costs,
I want Jarvis to be buried with the baby.
With a baby? Is the baby...
She said it was her baby with Ngai Ka-yan.
The baby just passed away?
No. Shortly before Mr. Ngai died.
But the baby is not yet 24 weeks,
the Government will not issue
a Certificate of Cremation.
They need to go somewhere else
to cremate the fetus
and get a different organization
for the burial.
Miss Lam didn't want the baby to be
cremated like a pet,
she left it in the hospital and
has been stalling.
The baby cannot be born because of us.
I want more than an arbitrary burial.
Hey!
What's this, Uncle?
None of your business. Give it back!
Hey, catch!
Hey...
Don't give it to him...
Hey, give it back!
Don't...
It's a gun!
Nice! Where did you get it?
It looks real.
It is real. Touch it and you're dead,
because I'm an undercover agent.
Uncle, you're a UC?
Mr. UC, where did you buy the gun?
Toy shop?
Can't fool you.
I got it from the toy shop over there.
You scraped the gun. Move aside.
You're no fun. Let's go.
Are you sure?
If you have money.
Is it a real gun?
We have a deal.
Did you see the look on that guy's face?
He tried to fool us with a toy gun,
thinking we were a bunch of kids.
Carl, next time quit while you're ahead.
We have unfinished business.
If we got busted,
we can't play anymore, OK?
OK...it won't happen again.
Jason, who's going in the water?
Whoever is the best swimmer.
Nobody?
What a bunch of losers!
Hey, Wendy!
I just decided...for the last video,
I'll go in the water.
How's your leg? Don't try to be brave!
What are you doing?
Run...
Can you manage?
Piece of cake.
I have fully recovered.
Nothing must go wrong, OK?
Since you let me join the group,
I know how important this is to you.
Wendy! Are you Wendy?
I don't know you. I have nothing
to say to you.
I'm Jason, a diehard fan of yours
and Jarvis'
Wendy, are you OK?
I saw you upload the video.
Why did you delete it?
I ran into a slight mishap.
Mishap? Relax, I still have a copy.
I'll send it to you and you can upload it.
Don't. The truth doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter?
Jarvis is dead. Why doesn't it matter?
I asked you to come to see if
you want to do something for Jarvis.
What?
J Weekly had a Static Apnea
Challenge before,
they meant to use one of these
to trick one of their own.
Wendy, why did you want me to say that?
You'll soon find out.
Look over here...
Excuse me...
Leaving already?
Bye, officer!
Thanks.
I finally know why you want me to say that.
You wanted to lure the cops over
and trick them.
Jarvis made a video of a prank on cops.
It had high viewership. We must do the same.
You want to make a ranking list?
Smart!
I didn't think of that.
What's next?
Wake up...
Get him...
In two months, we went from
not knowing how to shoot a video,
to having a bunch of diehard fans.
We have come this far,
I won't let this go down the drain.
I should thank you for taking the risk
of uploading the video in different places.
If IOY didn't have a special meaning for me,
I wouldn't rename the channel
and keep its name Agent J Channel.
He's my idol too.
We're kindred spirits.
I should thank you
for making videos to carry on
Jarvis' spirit.
Someone inspired me.
But Batman wouldn't want Robin
to go on like this.
What would he want Robin to do?
Pull yourself together
and do something meaningful.
For example, finish what he started...
Can I?
I can't believe I did it.
I will achieve Jarvis' target
and let him know he'll forever be
our spiritual leader.
This will be my last present for him.
But I have a question.
You won't tell us the target of
our next prank.
Is there a particular reason?
Clearing out today?
All good things must come to an end.
Anything else you need to ask about Wendy?
Before Ngai Ka-yan died,
was Wendy injured during filming?
Yes. Wendy on the Trampoline.
Jarvis made us aim for her sensitive areas.
Aim for her shirt, her chest...
Go to Hell!
Keep jumping...keep shooting...
He even threw Mr. Tsui's name in our face,
claiming he really bought the idea.
Hey!
Are you OK?
Well? Did you get it?
That's exactly what I want!
I like this shot.
Jarvis forced the shoot on us.
With no regard for Wendy's feelings.
I didn't expect our target to be an uncle.
This guy appears to be righteous,
but he's very sneaky,
making his pawns do his dirty work.
I have had enough of him.
Piece of cake. I'll think of a way
to lure him over.
No sweat! I'll get the job done.
Thank you.
I just looked at the video Tom mentioned.
It was livestreamed on the day
Wendy had a miscarriage.
It's highly likely the accident caused
Wendy's miscarriage.
She felt Jarvis knew she was pregnant
and still made her do that,
he wanted her to miscarry.
So she wanted to avenge the baby.
Happy birthday to you...
Gogo Sir, the story came out.
The headline reads "24-week baby cannot
be buried with parents"
"pray they will be united in Heaven".
There were 2,000 shares in half an hour.
The feed should reach Wendy soon.
Good.
My friend agreed to help with the feed
and announced the details of
Ngai Ka-yan's funeral.
Along with Cheong's writeup,
Wendy should be moved to tears
and show up to see Ngai Ka-yan
for the last time.
Let's hope so.
Then we can bring her in for questioning.
There's something I couldn't figure out.
On one hand, she hated Ngai Ka-yan.
On the other hand, she imitates his work
and arranged for his funeral.
That's so contradictory,
is she schizophrenic?
Is Wendy really the killer?
Let me show you something.
I went over all the videos on J Weekly
these past few days.
There were over a thousand!
I found this on the
behind-the-scenes footage.
Happy birthday to...
The IOY pin!
The pin belongs to Wendy.
That can prove she was inside
Ngai Ka-yan's office.
We have reason to believe
she swapped the cylinders.
Was it meticulously planned?
Or she killed him accidentally?
(Counting down to the game...)
Don't we have 36 hours to go?
Why only 22 hours left? That's tomorrow!
Why did they change the time?
In 22 hours...that should be...
Ngai Ka-yan's vigil.
We must keep a close watch.
Please sign here.
Didn't expect you to show up.
Anyway...may the deceased rest in peace.
(Counting down to the game...)
You're letting those kids do as they please?
They're crazy. They're capable of anything.
There's nothing we can do to stop them.
You guys and Jarvis started this trend.
How could you be so irresponsible?
Let's wait till after the funeral.
After the funeral?
If someone got killed in the prank,
how can you live with yourselves?
Miss Lok, can we have a word?
I know what you're worried about.
The funeral is a Police operation.
Don't give them a hard time.
Who's your target?
Wendy?
I knew it.
What do you know?
A few months ago when I visited my Mom,
she was preparing a Chinese herb decoction.
She said her colleague Wendy
had a miscarriage.
I didn't give that a second thought.
But since you arrested my Mom,
I've been thinking
who else had a motive to kill Jarvis.
I suddenly remember this
and I asked Mom about it.
She said Jarvis caused the miscarriage.
If Wendy was the killer,
another Static Apnea Challenge
may not be a simple prank.
You think it's another revenge?
Other than Jarvis,
did someone else cause Wendy's miscarriage?
He even threw Mr. Tsui's name in our face,
claiming he really bought the idea.
Tsui Chung-tai?
Mr. Tsui!
I didn't expect our target to be an uncle.
This guy appears to be righteous,
but he's very sneaky,
I have had enough of him.
Thanks for coming, Mr. Tsui.
Our livestreaming is about to begin.
The livestreaming started.
Mr. Tsui is at the scene.
Wendy is vicious to go after Mr. Tsui.
Help me, officer!
What do you want?
I need your help.
With what?
The Police found out I was with Jarvis
and he caused my miscarriage.
They should suspect me now.
You killed Jarvis?
Jarvis' funeral is tomorrow.
I really wanted to see him.
But I'm sure if I showed up
at the mourning hall,
the cops would arrest me.
You knew my Mom is in Lai Chi Kok
detention because of you.
How dare you waltz in here
and tell me this!
What if I turn you in?
Go ahead!
They don't have enough to nail me.
But on the contrary, Auntie Ching
admitted to swapping the cylinders,
she won't get away.
The Police will find a way.
Go ahead and call 999.
I'm certain after 48 hours,
the Police would let me go
because I won't cooperate.
But this won't do you or me any good.
You want me to send the cops away?
How could I do that?
Make something up.
Just say your Mom knew I was with Jarvis.
Tell them I had a miscarriage,
or your Mom helped me prepare
the decoction.
Convince Gogo Sir I have a second
target to kill.
Buy me time so I can see Jarvis.
I don't get it.
You said Jarvis caused the miscarriage.
Shouldn't you hate him?
Jarvis?
Sit down.
Dr. Leung told me you missed
your appointment.
Because I wasn't feeling well this morning.
Don't lie to me.
You obviously miscarried.
Why did you pretend you're pregnant?
Because I forced you onto the trampoline
and you lost the baby?
You pretended to be pregnant
to get even with me?
No, I did not. I was afraid you'd ditch me.
That's why I didn't tell you.
Silly girl. Who do you take me for?
I promised we'll have the baby
because I respect life.
Now that you tell me the baby is gone,
I couldn't wait to celebrate.
Wendy, you're still young.
Our channel is taking off,
having a baby now will hold us back.
You don't blame me?
Why would I?
Let's put this behind us
and focus on running the channel.
You'll always be my best partner, OK?
How stupid of you! For this man,
why feel so small and humble?
To think a baby can tie down Jarvis?
I was too naive.
Someone gifted like Jarvis
will not slow down for anyone.
That's crazy! I can't accept that.
That's why no one deserves to be
with him more than I do.
Others would only stop him
from soaring higher.
Only I understand.
He needs a quiet defender
who can help him realize his dream.
If you love him so much,
why did you kill him?
Gogo Sir is back with his team.
He just came inside the funeral home.
Wendy, you promised me
after you got your wish,
you'll clear Mom's name.
Come with me and turn yourself in.
Did you see Wendy?
No.
Lok Hiu-sin, what were you thinking?
You chose to help a murderer, of all people?
I really had no choice.
I don't want Mom to rot in detention.
Her health is deteriorating.
She can't take it much longer.
Wendy...promised she'll turn herself in.
I had to take a chance.
Turn herself in? Where is she now?
She said she got her wish,
but Jarvis hasn't.
Well? You let the last kid go?
Why not? He put on super glue,
can't pry open his mouth.
He didn't break any laws for pulling a prank
It's pointless to badger him.
If Helen didn't interfere,
we would have busted Wendy.
Look on the bright side,
we couldn't figure out what she was thinking
now at least we know she didn't do it
to avenge the baby.
I thought Wendy might have killed
Ngai Ka-yan for the baby,
but on second thought...
Auntie Ching brought the cylinder of
poison gas to the office.
She couldn't have known about it.
What then?
Wendy unknowingly killed Ngai Ka-yan?
Then why did she go inside the office
to swap the cylinders?
That's what I want to know.
But that's not what worries me...
If I killed someone I love by mistake,
I wouldn't know how to go on living.
(IOY Channel livestreaming will start soon)
(Thanks for everything.)
(See you around)
What's this? They're folding the channel?
Dream on!
IOY Season 2 officially begins.
After viewing the first season,
do you want more?
Me too. It's OK. We go with the flow.
We give you Season 2, right now,
right here...
We want to do something different.
All guys? No chicks?
Hold your horses.
We save the best for last.
Meet the star of J Weekly,
our spiritual leader, Wendy!
Long time no see! Did you miss me?
Long time no see!
I'm showing my face,
it means this is not full of crap.
We came up with a new game
called Lie Through Your Teeth.
We'll show you a term
and the three of them will take turns
to explain it.
Only one of them is telling the truth.
The other two are lying
but will pretend they're not.
Our viewers can vote
and guess who's telling the truth.
If nobody believes the person
telling the truth,
then this person will receive
a big punishment!
Without further ado, let's roll...
IOY Channel.
Take turns to explain IOY Channel.
Don't forget, only one of them
is telling the truth.
I'll go first.
IOY is short for I opt you.
To opt means to choose,
IOY stands for I choose you.
IOY came from someone I admire...
A ring box?
Jarvis wants to propose?
Wendy, where's the file?
Sorry, I saw this and thought it was cute.
So I took a look.
What's this?
I have never seen you wearing it.
See the letters on it?
Is it YOI?
Almost. It's IOY.
The year I started making videos,
I was named the most influential
online celebrity.
It was given to me as a gift
from the organizer.
IOY stands for Influencer of the Year.
This pin has great sentimental value.
I was afraid of losing it,
so I never wore it.
If you like it...you can have it.
But it has great sentimental value.
I'm not giving it to you for nothing.
You must try harder.
I have high hopes for you
as the next online celebrity.
I'll do my best.
My goal is to make this channel
the Influencer of the Year
and carry on Jarvis' spirit.
That's the meaning of IOY.
Yes...
Wendy made up a brilliant story.
But the viewers don't buy it...
The IOY bunch should be here.
Sir, this is Room 1208.
Looks like the viewers don't believe Wendy
is telling the truth.
Then we must...
Big punishment...
Open the door!
Big...
This is their hideout.
What are these weights for?
A clean cut on the rope,
not by natural wear and tear.
Climbing rope, weight...
they're testing something.
Your punishment is to get us snacks.
But from that island...
On a zip wire?
Of course! You want to walk?
Tens of thousands are waiting for you
to foot the bill.
A bet is a bet, and you lost.
These guys are nutcases.
They're livestreaming the zip wire?
Zip wires are not dangerous.
But these guys have a prior history.
God knows who's their next prey.
I think it's more than a prank.
Wait...I recognize this place.
Gogo Sir, TCD colleagues couldn't
decipher the livestreaming location.
What about the position?
They only know it's Tung Lung Island.
OK, let's split up. We'll try our luck.
We have done a rehearsal.
Just follow the rehearsal.
It's safe. Be careful.
Folks, Wendy is ready for her punishment.
Give loads of likes to encourage Wendy
Hello, Wendy...
I'm watching you on live.
Jarvis lied to you.
IOY doesn't stand for
Influencer of the Year.
It was a high school club called
Youth Investment Organization.
Jarvis and I both joined YIO.
That's why he had the pin.
Says who? You? Why should I believe you?
I don't know what game you're playing.
Don't risk your life over Jarvis' lie.
It's not worth it.
That's why Jarvis is the grandmaster.
In a few seconds, he came up with
a story to con me.
That's the craft of a master prankster.
More reason for me to finish this feat.
You knew he lied to you,
why follow through with it?
Whether or not I will succeed,
I must go through with it.
If Auntie Ching didn't bring the cylinder
of poison gas to kill Jarvis,
I would have tricked him
and earned his recognition.
Why? Why did you ruin it?
Hello? Wendy...
You again? The zip wire is perfectly legal.
Why must you butt in every time?
The zip wire is legal.
But you purposely sabotaged the rope
to pull a dangerous stunt.
That became my business.
You won't even bother to show proof
of a trumped-up charge?
Showing us a video can charge us
for a crime?
How dare you toy with an officer!
Gogo Sir, maybe you've been sitting
in your air-con office for too long.
You're so out of touch with the world.
This is what the viewers want.
They want something exciting and fun.
The more dangerous, the bigger the draw.
You're crazy!
Hey!
Sir!
Don't get rough...
Why did it stop?
It's not moving!
What happened? Pull her back in!
I don't know. During rehearsal,
she was in control. She...
Help! Can anyone help me?
I can't believe we already have a video
with over 300,000 views.
It's much quicker than the target
you set when you started the channel.
Not quick enough.
Not quick enough?
We don't have enough target audience.
When most people hear of prank videos,
they assume they're crude and small scale
and not presentable.
What do you have in mind?
I want to package it into a show,
just like a stage play or concert.
Something on a bigger stage,
reaching more people.
I know you can do it.
By then...maybe we can take a break.
Stop staring! Save her!
What's this?
It'll come in handy.
Wendy...yeah!
Gogo Sir, not need to overreact!
She fooled us all.
I watched her try the wristband.
It's an inflatable lifebuoy.
Everything was for this moment.
She staged the accident
during livestreaming.
Oh my God, why didn't I think of that?
Brilliant! Conning the viewers was easy,
but she fooled us too!
When she fell, I was really scared.
Wendy, wake up! Quit your act!
The livestreaming is finished.
She's not breathing! Call 999!
What?
Mom...
Wendy is dead.
I'm sorry, Mom! I can't help you.
I had ill intentions and wanted to
kill someone.
Perhaps...I deserved this punishment.
After Wendy died,
I checked her stuff and found this...
After several months' preparation,
I have finally come to this...
Yuen Kit-ching brought the poison gas
that killed Jarvis,
I was angry at first.
But I let it slide.
Because Jarvis is dead.
The key is how to pass on his spirit
so he would approve of me wherever he is.
Accidents happen,
that's why I decided to record this.
Because I promised Helen,
I would reveal the truth about
Jarvis' death.
That day when I mixed up the cylinder of
oxygen with the gas for the starter horn,
Tom and Paul rushed over and nervously
tried to stop me.
I found that rather odd.
Later Jarvis told me those two ingrates
planned to trick him with a stink bomb.
So he decided to trick them with
an oxygen cylinder.
On the day of the Challenge,
Paul and I had to do another livestreaming.
While we were getting ready,
I saw Jarvis go inside his office,
and put a blue cylinder in the drawer.
Right then, I knew he planned to use it
to trick Tom and Paul.
Around that time, Daisy was
hanging around Jarvis,
and Jarvis seemed to enjoy it.
He even let her host the Challenge.
Remember to CLS. See you next time, bye!
Good! Help me clean this up.
I still have a video call.
It was 1:50p.m. when Paul and I finished.
You did great!
Thanks.
I'll let you take care of this.
I took the garbage to the back stairs,
when I passed by the pantry,
I saw Auntie Ching making sweet soup.
Paul went inside the conference room
for his video call.
I went back inside but didn't see
Auntie Ching in the pantry.
I went back inside the office,
and saw Auntie Ching holding a blue cylinder
and snuck inside Jarvis office.
I saw her swap the cylinder she was holding
with the one Jarvis put inside the drawer.
When I look at the cylinder,
I thought it was the stink bomb
Tom prepared.
My first reaction was Auntie Ching
wanted to trick Jarvis.
But soon afterwards, I saw her
switch them back.
I thought maybe she was afraid Jarvis
would find out.
Right then, Daisy suddenly came to mind...
Daisy?!
You have time for an interview?
For you? Anytime.
Wendy, get us some tea.
Thank you.
If the Challenge was a hit,
Daisy may take my place.
On the contrary, if I finished what
Auntie Ching dared not do,
when Jarvis found out I pulled
a prank on him,
he'd be so surprised and impressed.
So I went to get the stink bomb
that was left behind.
But I accidentally knocked over the vase.
I didn't want anyone to see me,
so I hid myself.
Who broke this?
I don't know.
I was in the supplies room checking
the props of the Challenge.
I heard the noise and came to check it out.
Did you check on the weight belts?
Not yet.
Can you check while I run to the toilet?
Auntie Ching, something is broken,
can you clean this up?
Luckily, nobody saw me.
Paul called out to Auntie Ching to
clean up the shards.
Since Auntie Ching wasn't holding anything,
I figured she left the cylinder
in Jarvis' office.
Once I got inside,
I looked for the cylinder.
I didn't expect Auntie Ching
to hide it so well.
After I swapped the cylinders,
Auntie Ching and Tom were still cleaning
the shards in the hallway
so I stayed there a bit longer.
Don't cut yourself.
Soon afterwards, I heard Jarvis came in
with Auntie Ching and Tom.
I walked out from the pantry
and Jarvis ordered us to head down
to the pool to set up.
You picked the small one
and left the big one for me.
You're stronger.
As I was heading out, from the corner
of my eye
I saw Jarvis take the cylinder
from the drawer.
I thought I'd hit a home run
and would be able to trick Jarvis.
But he died after he inhaled
from the cylinder.
Hey...are you OK?
Jarvis...
Are you OK?
Hey...
Don't scare me...
Wake up...
My mind went completely blank.
I thought Daisy took the cylinder
prepared by Tom and Paul.
Tom never got along with Jarvis,
did Daisy work with him to kill Jarvis?
Later, I found out it wasn't Daisy.
Then why did Auntie Ching do it?
Where did she get the poison gas?
Did she take it from Tom?
Is Tom the killer?
Auntie Ching already quit.
Why?
Why did Auntie Ching quit?
Is she really scared?
Wendy! Are you Wendy?
Jason later sent me a video.
It was Jarvis who paralyzed Helen.
How is Helen related to the online channel?
Mom, how nice of you to pick me up
from work?
So I followed Helen
and found out Auntie Ching is Helen's Mom.
The gas came from Auntie Ching.
She wanted to kill Jarvis
but couldn't do it.
I wanted Jarvis recognition
and killed him by mistake.
No!
Auntie Ching deleted the video
but I had no intention to inform the Police.
I don't want the cops to stop me
from carrying on Jarvis' legacy.
I know I will succeed. Jarvis will see it.
Where did this come from?
The GoPro when she was on the zip wire?
Wendy considered Ngai Ka-yan her idol.
Like him, she died in front of the camera.
Helen just finished giving her statement.
From Lam Sum-ling's phone,
we found a self-made video
that can prove Auntie Ching removed
the poison gas.
Legally, that won't constitute as murder.
But she stole a hazardous gas,
she's guilty of possession of a dangerous
substance and theft.
She cannot post bail yet.
Ngai Ka-yan, I never understood why
you enjoy being a prankster.
Because you were deprived of love?
You want other people's attention?
Mom, I want to play in the park.
Ten minutes.
What?
Ngai Ka-yan, when I bought you
the watercolor,
what did you promise me?
Play less and study more.
I'll pick you up in 20 minutes.
Yeah...
Who did this?
Why?
Superman against monsters...
Ngai Ka-yan, it's wrong to trick other kids.
I understand.
I bought you a sketch book.
You can take it out and share with
other kids.
Why must you do this?
I know.
Let's go.
Mom, there's a mosquito on your back.
Let me swat it for you.
OK, it's dead.
Good boy. Thank you.
I remember that time at the
high school playground,
I told you your prank paralyzed me.
I wanted you to stop tricking people,
but you wouldn't listen.
Perhaps you were born that way.
There's no reason for it.